大家好，我是Anna Silk
Hi everyone I'm Anna Silk
欢迎来到季前秀
and welcome to the club house
我和妖女迷行的演员们在一起
I’m here with the Lost Girl cast
还有不到一小时第四季就首播了
and we're getting ready for the premiere of season4 in just under an hour.
我们会回答一些大家提出的问题，讨论一下剧情
We're going be answering fan questions and chatting about life
再看点小片段和先行剧
and having a little movie night and viewing the webisodes.
那么，首先请大家自我介绍一下吧
So let's have everyone introduce themselves.
我扮演的是外公Trick
Hi I'm Rick Howland I play Trick
我扮演的是怪蜀黍Vex
I’m Paul Amos and I play Vex
我是Rachel Skarsten，我扮演Tamsin
I’m Rachel Skarsten I play Tamsin
我是Ksenia Solo，我扮演Kenzi
I’m Ksenia Solo,and I play Kenzi
Kris Holden Ried,Dyson
我是Zoie Palmer，我演Lauren Lewis医生
I’m Zoie Palmer and I play doctor Lauren Lewis
我是K.C.Collins, 我演Hale
And I’m K.C. Collins and I play Hale
我是Anna，我演Bo
And I’m Anna and I play Bo
第三季离我们已经有一段时间了
It's been a while since season three
那么，让我们回顾一下上一季的主要片段吧
so let’s take a look back and see where we left off
我将如他一般称王
I will reign as he did
即使死亡也会畏惧我们
Even death will fear us
只有我才能决定谁生谁死
Only I will choose who lives
这只是冷静一下，对吧
This is just a break, right
不，请告诉我她不是那个人
No,please tell me she's not the one
你上次给人类做手术是什么时候？
When was the last time you...actually operated on the human?
放心
Relax
你很快就不是人类了
This is the last time you'll be human
我要求投票表决不信任这个假Ash
I call a vote of no confidence in this fake Ash
M女王刚宣布你是王座之敌
The Morrigan just declared you the enemy of the realm
在你安全之前我是不会离开你的
I'm not leaving your side till you are safe
你很强悍，Kenzi
You are tough, Kenzi
可你是个人类
But you are human
很快就不会是了
Not for long
我们总有一天得死
We all gotta die someday
停车！
Stop the car!
哦哦哦哦~ 没错就是酱紫
Ohhhhh man yes
我俩得多谢《末路狂花》了，你懂的(对)
Thanks for going all Thelma and Louise on me there Rach (ya) you know
*Thelma and Louise 末路狂花 1991年美国电影，以两主角驾车冲下悬崖结尾*
跳崖什么的啥时候这么爽过
Never look better going off a cliff
上一季真的发生了许多事情呀
A lot happen last season huh guys?
对的没错，上一季的确发生了许多事情（例如？)
Yes a lot did happen last season(like what)
恩，包括...
well including
包括我有小山姆啦~
the birth of my son Sam
能跟我的LG家庭分享这一刻真的是美好无比
It’s great to share this time with my Lost Girl family
每个人都很欢迎Sam
everyone has welcome Sam
这也是第四季里超级重要的一部分
and it's been a big part of season 4
所以我想把山姆介绍给大家
and I just wanna to introduce him to you guys
不过现在已经过了他上床睡觉的时间了
but it is just past Sam's bed time
所以他现在要准备睡觉觉啦
so he's gonna to sleep now
晚安山姆
so good night Sam
晚安（晚安）
Good night sam x6
没错，我相信你们绝对会认同我
Yal I think you guys would definitely agree with me
我们有世界上最棒的粉丝对吗？
when I say that we have the greatest fans in the world. yes?
是的没错 （绝对的啦）
Yes we do   totally
所以，我们这有个神奇的盒子，里面装满了
So we actually have a magical fae box full of questions
大家写给我们的问题
that you guys have written name with
那么一起来看看吧
So let’s see we are wanna know
第一个问题来自Nikki Claire
First question from Nikki Claire
你们在哪里长大以及你们小时候是怎样的
Where did you grow up and what were you like as a kid?
哦……
Ooooh....
从你开始吧KC
let's start with you KC
我在....
I grew up...
大多数时间在多伦多，然后还有别的许多地方
for the most part in Toronto,and a lot of other places.
但如果是最纯粹的最好的话，那么还是多伦多
But to keep it nice and not complicated so Toronto
我小的时候很好动
and as a kid I was athletic
我觉得我跟战神金刚一样
I felt like I was a defender of the universe.
真好（哇）
It's nice (wow)
我能保护所有人
I defended a lot of people
并且，我打赢了好多架（厉害！）
and I ended up in a lot of fights.(cool)
不过我奶奶对此不是很高兴啊 （哈哈哈哈）
That my grandma wasn't happy about.-hehehe
佐，你呢？
How about you Zo?
恩，我在英格兰的Cornwall郡的Camborne长大
I grew up in Camborne,Cornwall,England
直到十岁搬到这边
until I was about ten.And then we moved here.
我是个打了鸡血的人
I was hyper
恩，真是个鸡血娃
like I was really hyper kid.
别忘了，你跟我住一个村呢
Don't forget Zo, you lived in the same village as me,too
哦，还有威尔士，我还在威尔士住过
And Wales,I lived in Wales,too.
噢，你们居然住在村子里
Oh you guys lived in a village.
是呀是呀~~
Yeah oh yeah
噢，我是个城市娃啊~
oh boy.I'm a city boy.
恩，我在Fredericton, New Brunswick长大
I grew up in Fredericton, New Brunswick
我小时候什么样的？
And what was I like.
恩....我想跟现在完全一样
I was kind of exactly like I am now,I think.
我还真花过一整个夏天的时间把自己打扮成神奇女侠
But I did spent an entire summer dressed as a wonder woman.
毫不夸张的说，像是在我家小区内打击犯罪什么的
Like literally,fighting crime in my neighberhood.
没错，我每天穿一样的衣服
Yes.I wore same thing everyday.
怎么个打击法？
How was that one fight?
我是说，拜托，那是New Brunswick耶
I mean come on,it's New Brunswick
嘿，一些事情在那发生了好吗？
Hey! Some stuff happens there,OK.
有没这么巧，我也是玩神奇女侠长大的
Strangely enough, I grew up also playing wonder woman.
所以我整天戴着我的手镯到处溜达
So I walked around with my bracelets.
你真的是认真的？
Are you being serious?
当然啦
Yes I am.
我超爱神奇女侠
I love wonder woman.
我，我在拉脱维亚的Riga长大
Me.I grew up in Riga, Latvia
我小的时候，我记得我喜欢....
As a kid,I just remenber love...
我喜欢童话故事
loving fairytales.
没有什么比听故事更好玩的事情了
There's nothing better than being told a story.
所以这大概也是为什么我想成为演员的原因吧
So I think that's why I wanted to become an actor.
我非常喜欢那些故事里面生动的情节
Cuz I just love the art of story telling so much.
好的，Rachel呢？
OK,Rachel?
我在加拿大的多伦多长大的
I grew up in Toronto,Canada.
小的时候，我真的是十分女生的女生
And as a little girl, I was very much a girly girl.
我所有的东西都是粉红色的（不会吧？！）
Everything was pink  (What?!)
恩，我知道很雷
Yeah,I know,Shocking.
我曾是个软妹子
I was a girly girl
现在却成了个女汉子
Cause I'm like a dude now,you know,so
闭嘴
shut up.
Paul 你呢？
How about you,Paul?
我，恩，我在威尔士的一个小村庄里长大
I eh...well I grew in a little village in Wales.
我们讲的那种有趣的霍比特人语言叫威尔士语
Where we used to speek a little funny hobbit language called Welsh.
“要是我在说威尔士语，听起来就像这样”
恩，语言很好听，一起的人也很友善
So it's a beautiful language,surounded by beautiful people
是个美丽的山村啊
and beautiful countryside
所以我觉得能在那长大真幸运
and I'm very very luky to grow up there.
那你是怎么变成现在这个凶残样的
And how did you turn out to be so evil?
就是，我们都不知道这之后发生了什么
We don't know what happened after that
我会告诉你的
I'll tell you what happened.
我会告诉你么
我爷爷是个说相声的
My grandfather was a compair.
就像是酒吧里的那种
Which is like an MC in the club.
所以他经常在酒吧里又唱又跳还经常讲点笑话神马的
So he used to like entertain and sing and tell jokes in the clubs.
然后把，我叔叔经常偷偷把我带去那
And mu uncle used to smuggle me in the clubs
所以我就能坐在桌子上
so I could on the table
看我爷爷怎么样娱乐400多号人
and watch my grangfather entertain like 400 people.
哇哦，我的天，你怎么样外公？
Oh my god.How about you Rickster?
我在安大略的Kingston出生
Ah...I was born in Kingston, Ontario
就这附近
Eh just down the road.
我是个厉害的小孩，因为我好像无所不知
I was a sarcastic child. Bit of a Know-it-all.
所以你懂，就这样
So you know, there you go
哦，太棒了，就像是命定的一样
Oh ,perfect.It's like the fate...
对啊，我现在还是跟以前一样
Yeah I didn't fall far from the tree.
角色与我一脉相承
From my character's tree.
下一个问题，来自Valkenzfae
Next question,Ok.from Valkenzfae
对于所有剧中神奇生物来说
Of all the mythological creature that have been on the show
如果有机会改变的话，你们最想变成什么
which one would you wanna be if you had the chance?
沼泽地那个
The swomp one.
沼泽地那个？
The swamp one?
*应该是指河童那集*
你想脏兮兮又冷冰冰还湿淋淋的？
You wanna be muddy and cold? And wet?
还有那个脑袋？
With the head?
瑞秋的品味很独特啊~
Rachel's got a weird taste at things.
就是长成那样
It's just get to look like that.
还跳出来啊啊啊啊的吓人
And come out to me like WAAA
好的小伙伴们我们来看个粉丝的视频问题
OK,guys.Let's check out a fan video question.
这来自Audrie
This is from Audrie.
认真的说
Professionally talking
推特有没改变什么
Did Twitter change something
要是有的话，是什么？
and if yes, what?
另外，我爱你们大家
P.S. I love you guys
Audrie我们也爱你
We love you too Audrie!
谢谢你的问题和你一直的支持
Thank you for your question and your endless support!
是啊
Yeah.
她可是我们的资深粉了
She's been one of our biggest fans from the very beginning.
这剧能成功神马的都是她的功劳
I think she's the reason that the show's successful
是啊，单枪匹马
Yeah, single handedly.
你知道什么很疯狂吗
Do you know what has been crazy though
就是推特影响力这么大
is how big twitter has become now
上季首播我们是推上关键字第一
and the fact that on the last season premier it was trending NO.1.
我还记得我当时坐那
I remember exactly where I was sitting.
我想我得看看流行关键字啥样
And I am like eh I'm just gonna see what's the trending like...
啥？啥？
WHAT!WHAT!
然后我就打给每个熟人
and then just call everybody that I knew
说赶紧的，上推上推
and was like"You have to go on twitter right now!Go on twitter!"
那真是好疯狂，好大影响力
And that was wild.I mean,that was really huge.
是，那就是证明
Yeah. It is a testament,too
给我们的观众和粉丝的
to our viewers and our fans.
好，我们现在要休息一下，进段网络剧
OK,we are doing to take a break for a webisode now.
第三季结尾，Kenzi和Bruce开着超酷的跑车绝尘而去
And at the end of season3 Kenzi and Bruce sped off in a very sexy car
去找Massimo
in search of Massimo.
我想知道他俩路上如何
I wonder what would a road trip with these two be like,
除了吃曲奇多听辣妹
Besides,you know eating lots of Cheetos and listening to Spice Girls.
来看看吧
Let's check it out
别说了，Brucy
End of discussion,Brucy
我再过一个桥就到了
I'm one bridge away from getting what I need
不成功便成仁
It's Druid or bust
但是Kenzi,Massimo可不是什么良民
But Kenzi,Massimo is not a nice person
行行好，善良就跟紧身裤一样过时了
Please,nice is yesterday's skinny jeans
Kenzi现在需要的是今日残酷的现实
What Kenzi needs is today's brutal truth
现实就是现在都异种末日了
and the truth is that it's Faemageddon out there
姐也得准备战斗
so I need to armor up
直面现实吧，到了考验我的时候了
Faced out,this is human check for a while
可我是异种，我的人生也不见得有多美好
But I'm Fae and my life is not exactly peaches and cream
你总算还有天赋，我呢，切……
Yeah well,at least you still got presents,me,blahh...
看吧，姐连路都不会走了
You see,I can barely even walk!
是你鞋子的问题，跟太高了
It's your shoes. They are too tall
你在逗我？我们大风大浪都过来了
Really?After everything you and I've been through?
你却吐槽我的鞋子？
You are dissing my kicks?
吐槽？我从来不吐槽
Diss? I never diss
哼
Ha
我都不知道怎么吐槽
I don't even know how to diss!
等等
Kenzi wait
危险
Danger
这里危机四伏
It's everywhere
禁止通过
Passage denied!
谁说的？
Says who?
滚粗，六
Up yours,six
滚粗...七？
Up yours...seven?
那是我的网名，眼线女
That's my handle,eyeliner
不过你大概理解不能
You probably wouldn't understand
因为你都只听男人的嘛
You are used to the man telling you how it is
男人，表想！男孩，更死开！
Men,niet,boys never!
尤其是你这种肮脏邋遢的下流货
Especially not scrufy pit stain maggots
不好意思，你那渣渣的90年代最炫哥特风叫太大声
Sorry your trash can goth rag is screaming 90s too loud
我听不清
I can't hear you!
是吗，你这个杀马特洗剪吹要是不懂时尚的话
Oh really? Well I'm sorry if you can't stay in style you main stream hipster poser
就给我死远些
then get off the runway
这……
Hmm...
艾马，我们遇到了个巨魔
Oh boy,we've got a Troll
姐没跟你说话
You am I not talking to
但我要是在跟你说话，我会问
but if I was I'd be all like
是那种放弃治疗又丑穷挫的巨魔吗？
what like under the bridge fugly Troll?
不是，是网上的脑残（词同巨魔）
No,an internet Troll
那些脑残还真是巨魔？
Those are like actual Trolls?
没错
Ugh-huh
噢娘啊……嘿，小六子
Oh boy...Hey six!
你现在不是该在网上四处掐架吗？
Shouldn't you be like online,pissing people off?
我匿名掐得太狠了点
I trolled a little bit too awesomely on anonymous
他们就把我给黑了
They had me hacked
被关小黑屋一个月
transferred for a month
噢，巨魔村的旧闻
Hmmm the old time Bridgeville,well BAM!
又出现在了凡人的新大陆上，不是很讽刺么？
And in mortal worlds of Mygrossatlantis isn't it ironic?
还有一周我就解放了，好吧？
I only have a week left OK?
噢~你这是要哭的节奏吗？
Oh are you gonna cry?
要我给你擦那副没度数的甜心霍利眼镜吗？
Do you want me to polish up those non-precription Buddy Holly glasses for you?
*巴蒂霍利Buddy Holly 美国40年代摇滚歌手，以黑框眼镜闻名*
你很尖酸，很聪明，还很可恶
Oh you are sharp,and smart,and nasty
行了童鞋们，冲突让我觉得不舒服
Come on guys,confrontation makes me itchy
我们再来一次,我叫Bruce
Let's start over, I'm Bruce
噢！！！ Bruce！
Oh!!! Bruce...
很高兴认识你，Bruce!
Nice to meet you,Bruce!
天啊，你一个瘦子打人还真痛
Oh! God for a skinny guy you sure pack a lot of punch!
没错，巨魔
Yeah, Troll!
听着，我得去你守着的这个
Look I need to get to a Druid on the other side of that bridge,
桥那头去
the bridge that you've been signed to guard
这是你要拯救世界的节奏？
One of the Caption X position?
*Captain X: DC 超级英雄*
好吧，你想怎么着？
OK, how is this gonna work?
要我付钱吗？还是要我的一缕头发？
Do you want me to do some kind of payment, a lock of my hair?
笑死我了，拿来做成牙线剔牙一周吗？
Hahaha,and be flossing whiff for my teeth for a week?
不了，谢谢
No thank you
说得就像你要拿来吃一样
Ya,if you were eating it
额滴神啊，你要吃我吗？
Oh my God are you gonna eat me?
不会，只要你在这签个名
Not if you sign here
啥，你要我帮你守桥？
What you want me to take over guarding the bridge?
你太适合这工作了，你挖苦人跟我一样厉害
You're perfect for the gate. You spit back insult as fast as I do
但你说还得守一个星期啊
Yeah but you have like a week left
对啊，没什么大不了的对吧
Exactly,so,it's no biggy,right?
反正你画个眼妆也得那么久
I mean what is that,as long as you apply your eye make up?
老娘现在就要见Massimo
I need to see Massimo,now
除非你在这签名
Not until you sign here
看姐美丽的嘴唇，不！
Read my perfectly lined lips,no!
嘤嘤嘤嘤
Sob sob
呃……没事的……
Em...OK,it's OK
乖，不哭不哭，乖
It's alright. Don't cry. It's alright
小六子亲，别哭了，姐不把人喷哭的
six honey, come on, I don't speak sad troll
冷静，冷静，深呼吸
just,just slow down.slow down,take a breath
来，跟Kenzi船长说说是怎么回事？
then tell Kenzi Kirk, what's wrong
恩，就是一个月前
Well, you see it was about a month ago
我在网上遇到了个叫Owen的
I was online and I met this guy name Owen
明天本该是我们头一次约会
And tomorrow was supposed to be our first like date
就在个咖啡馆兼游戏厅兼折纸工作室
at this coffee shop/game room/oragami workshop
噢，红色康乃馨
Ahh,the red carnation
这样他就能认出你来
So he knows it's you
很传统，姐喜欢
Old school,I like it
但是见面时间是中部2点
But it's like 2 central,OK?
我又不能擅离职守
because I can't leave the bridge unguarded
算了，无所谓
Well doesn't even matter
反正哥不用粗犷的口气喷人就连话都说不来了，看吧
I can't talk to anyone without insulting them with roadtrip breath,see?
好吧，你喜欢攻击人是因为你觉得你很聪明
OK,emm,so you like insulting people because you think you are clever?
脑残妹，我就是很聪明
I am clever,no-lobes
恩，那你干嘛不用你的聪明才智说点好听的？
Ugh huh,so why don't your try being clever by saying something nice?
试试
Try me
我看着你的裤子一点都不想呕吐
Your pants, don't even make me wanna puke
好，初战告捷，不过不说呕吐成吗？
OK, great first try, but emm let's pin the puke and try again
假设我是Owen
I'm Owen
你网上的切格瓦拉名言警句合集
Your online collection of Che Guevara quotes
*切格瓦纳有个戴贝雷帽的经典造型*
让人家想给自己编朵贝雷帽
make me want to knit my own beret
对，没错，就是这样
Yes that's it, totally! OK!
那么这个桥……
So about the bridge
唉，姐就是一朵浪漫的女纸
Huh,I'm such a sucker for love
别
No!
少管闲事！
Mind your own business!
Kenzi的事就是我的事
你这网上药不能停的中二病患者
Kenzi is my business, you internet cockraoch jagrag!
Bruce,没事的
Bruce,it's OK
你也是
And you
你压根就不知道你自己有多弱爆
You have a deep shit of misconception about how little power you have over people!
但是你是我盆友，我无条件支持你
But you are my friend, and I support you
就算你的鞋子根本就走不了路
even if your shoes are ridiculously road trip unfriendly!
噢他战斗力挺高啊，赶得上论坛水军了
Oh he's good! Like online message board good
是啊，谁知道呢？
Ya, who knew?
我才不想替他执勤，但是要是能让你高兴的话
I don't like being this person,but I'll do it if it makes your happy
把合同给我就是了
So just...just give me the contract
谢了兄弟，要握个手吗？
Thanks dude,can I shake your hand?
我能把你的手捏爆吗？
Can I crush it?
祝我好运吧，顺便说一句，鞋子不错，犀利
Wish me luck,P.S. love the shoes,fierce
谢谢！好运！玩得开心！
Thanks! Good luck! Have fun!
我爱你Kenzi，但是要是发生了什么事
I love you Kenzi,but if anything happened...
闭嘴
Shut up
你闭嘴
You shut up
你闭上你的嘴
You shut your mouth
嘴闭上的你
You shut your face!
滚粗，把门带上
Shut the front door!
出门的时候别被门夹了屁股
Don't let it hit your ass on your way out
桥的事，还有其他所有事，都谢谢你了
Thank you,for guarding this bridge,for everything
感谢你是你
Thanks for being you
不要信任Massimo
Don't trust Massimo
我保证
Promise
绝不要怀疑大块头
Never suspect the big ones
太好了，好可爱
Lovely! (Awesome!)
真是不错的关系
It's a nice relationship
我喜欢看他俩在一起，因为我觉得
I love seeing them together because I feel like they're both looking for...
他俩都在寻找栖身之所
you know,their place in the world
Kenzi为Bruce的困难感到难过
And I think Kenzi feels bad that Bruce had this,you know,really hard life and really hard
她感同身受
so she relates to him
我觉得是挺美好的友谊
I think it's a beautiful friendship
好的小伙伴们我们休息一会儿
OK guys we're gonna take a break
回来的时候，会有更多网络剧
But when we come back,more webisode
还有我超想看的幕后花絮
some bloopers that I'm super excited to see
以及更多的粉丝问题
And some more of your fan questions
等下再见
So see you soon
恩大家好我是K.C.欢迎回来
Well hello I'm K.C and welcome back to the Clubhouse
今晚我们在这对妖女迷行畅所欲言
We're here tonight talking about everything Lost Girl
为第四季首播做准备
And to get ready for the season 4 premier
我们收到了粉丝的狂多问题
We have tons of questions from the fans
第一个问题，来自Shirley R.Wilde
And the first question here is, from Shirley R.Wilde,
是问Anna和Zoie的
and it's for Anna and Zoie
她俩挺狂野
Who surely are wild
*谐音笑话*
干得好，先生，干得好
Well done,sir,well done. ok.
Bo和Lauren是如此不同的两个个体
Bo and Lauren are opposites on so many levels
但她俩爱得伟大，爱得投入
Yet their love is phenomenal and inevitable
恩，你觉得是为什么呢？
OK. Why do you think that is?
反面的吸引力
Opposites attract
确实没错，还有我觉得Lauren来说
Definitely there's that. And also I think that for Lauren
Bo是为数不多，我说Lauren经常像个局外人
Bo is one of the few people...like Lauren feel like an outsider in a lot of ways
因为她是人类
because she's a human
异种随便就能把她扔到一边了
and at any moment could have been sort of tossed aside by the fae
我觉得Bo也是从人类世界出来的
I think that because Bo comes from a world in which she kind of started as a human
某种意义上来说
just some degree, or seems that way
我们多少有点……
that we kind off had some...
我有点依赖你的感觉
I think I clanged onto you a little bit
我觉得要和Zoie Palmer不产生火花挺难
I would find it hard to not have chemistry with Zoie Palmer
因为她漂亮又聪明
Cause she's beautiful and smart and...
你也一样，你也漂亮
You're those things too. You're beautiful too
别说了
Shut up.
好了好了
All right,all right.
回到这边
So here we go
这个问题来自Daniel Miller，他说
This one's from Daniel Miller, and he says...
我喜欢宣传片里那个wanderer的歌
I love the Wanderer song covered in the promo
他想知道是哪来的和他在哪能找到
He wants to know where did it come from and can he get it.
好问题，好故事
Well it's a good question and a good story
Jay Firestone，我们的执行制片
Cuz Jay Firestone,our executive producer
和Vanessa Piazza，我们的一个超棒的制片
and emmm...Vanessa Piazza one of our amazing producers
他们在一起面试了好多女歌手
And they got together,and they actually held auditions for female vocalists to come in to cover the song
然后这个，有一个，她叫……
And the one that...one of the...her name is...
Emily Mover
Emily Mover (Emily Mover)
M-O-V-E-R
在Showcase.ca上也可以下载
And it's available on Showcase.ca
请来加点酒
Qu'en serves un peu plus de vin,s'il vous plait.
*此处狼叔和KS说的是法语*
多谢，Bruce
Ah merci beaucoup, Bruce
嗨Bo你好（你好Bruce你怎么样？）
Hi Bo, how are you (I'm good Bruce how are you)
啊狼人
Oh wolfman
相信我，我比你更怕现在
I'm more afraid than you are right now, trust me
谁最能instagram
Who's the best instagramer
*Instagram 一款支持用户选择图片滤镜样式及多平台一键分享的移动拍照APP*
哦小伙伴们来投票吧
Oh guys let's see the vote
谁最能instagram
Who is the best instagramer
我，我不……
I, I don't...
肯定是沙发上这仨里的一个
Like it's gotta be one of these three on the couch here
我就不用instagram
cause I don't instagram
我不知道，我高高在上，我就说
I don't know, I think I'm high up there. I just wanna say.
我觉得Kris的照片拍得美得要命
I feel like Kris takes phenomenally artistic beautiful photos
但Ksenia Solo参加摄影比赛了
The thing is, Ksenia Solo entered a competition for her photographs
对！没错！
Yeah! yes!
我记得Ksenia获奖了
Yeah I think Ksenia win
你参加竞赛绝对自动获奖
If you are entering competitions, you just automatically win
好了小伙伴们这里有个另外的视频问题
OK guys there's another video question
真好，我们来听听吧，听
Sweet. Shall we get to it? Let's get to it
我们想知道组里大家的性格
We want to know more about people's personalities on set, like...
谁是搞笑的
who's the funny one
谁是公主病，不出拖车
And who is the diva, who never comes out of their trailer
说“别看我，别跟我讲话”
and says "don't look at me, don't even talk to me"
谁是飙戏大师
Who is the serious meth-head actor
谁是搞怪王
And who is the practical joker
我是公主病，我从来不出拖车
I'm the diva, I never leave my trailer
我几乎不……
No I hardly...
我不觉得有人是公主病
I'm not sure if any of us here is diva, really
我是说，有些人是要花点时间出来见人
I mean, some of us are slower to come out of our trailers than others...
你知道吗
You know what
某男总是花不少时间梳妆打扮
The guy who always take a little extra time
是有点公主诶
It's a bit of a diva, yeah
谁是搞怪王
Who's a practical joker
我觉得不是你就是Kris
I think either you or Kris
啥？
What!?
绝对是你俩其中之一
Yeah, it's between you two
对我们天天互相搞怪
But we're just like practically joking each other
没错
That's true
看吧，选出来了
Well there you go
Kris拍着拍着就脱裤子
Kris does every other scene with his pants down
或者拿个吉他在手上
Yeah, or a guitar on his hand or...
我老说你真人性格比我更像Kenzi
I always say, you're actually more like Kenzi in your real life than you're like Dyson
所以他演Kenzi真是小事一桩
So when you played Kenzi it was like there's no biggie
Kris终于可以本色演出了
Kris finally gets to play himself
噢噢噢噢噢
Wohooo~
我觉得真是不错
I think it's a good time
另一个网络剧，Trick和Hale一直是密友
For another webisode, Trick and Hale have always had a very tight relationship
作为新的Ash, Hale视Trick为导师
As the new Ash, this year Hale really uses Trick as a mentor
下一个网络剧将有幸见到他俩在Trick回到酒吧后重逢
This next webisode was a nice chance to see the two backed together after Trick gets back to the Dal
让我们看第二集网络剧，预言
Let's take a look at the second webisode Prophecy
啊，这里就像僵尸世界大战的战场似的
Ah it's like World War Z happened here.
*World War Z 由Brad Pitt主演的动作片*
欢迎回来，Brad Pitt
Welcome home, Brad Pitt.
你在这干嘛？
What are you doing here?
把邮件捎给你？
Bringing your mail?
人家扔你门口了
Someone left it on your doorstep.
然后顺便看看情况
And I'm checking up on things.
不当Ash了我闲得发慌
Being the former Ash,well that leaves a lot free time on your hands.
不用谢我了
You're welcome.
知道我的酒吧发生了什么事吗？
Any idea what happened to my bar?
呃，复仇女神闯进来开了个趴？
Emm...Furies broke in and threw a party?
说到开趴
Oh speaking of party
你的性福之旅怎样了？
how was your sex-cation?
别提这壶……
Just...don't...
喔，抱歉，不知道你跟Stella分手了
Oooh,sorry I didn't know that you and Stella split.
好吧，恩，跟我聊聊
Alright,well,talk to me.
好吧
Well
你听说那句名言
you know the saying
离别是如此甜蜜的凄婉
parting is such a sweet sorrow.
*出自罗蜜欧与朱丽叶第二幕第二场*
然后？
Yeah?
爷的离别更“甜”
I've had sweeter.
女人啊
Women...
没错
Ugh huh.
以及爱她们的那些傻蛋
And the fools who love them.
就算再破（也是自己的家）
Be it ever so humble.
*出自19世纪名歌 Home Sweet Home，意指家再破旧也是自己的家*
要不就是家里剩下来的东西
What's left of it.
现在来说正事
Now to attend to my first love.
我给你泡点茶吧
I'll make you some tea.
请跟我说你见过Kenzi了
Please tell me you've seen Kenzi.
你是我进门见的第一个熟人
You're the first familiar face I've seen come through that door.
她短信我说她没事
She sent me a text message saying she was Ok.
我只是不知道她在哪
It's just I don't know where she is.
还有Dyson和Tamsin
Dyson and Tamsin on the other hand
我甚至不知道他们是死是活
I don't even know if they are alive.
我对这里发生的事有种很坏的感觉
I have a bad feeling about what happened here.
啊这些你拉几个壮劳力就能修复了
Ah nothing that a bucket of elbow grease that can't fix.
这是毛？
What's this?
务必小心轻拿轻放
Ah...be very careful with that.
看起来像某种异种通灵板
Looks like some kind of Fae Ouija board.
*Ouija board 外观及性能均类似碟仙*
这是一个古老又强大的占卜板
It's a very old, very powerful divination planque.
我还以为我刚说的就这意思
I believe that's what I just said.
真的？
Really?
你以为德尔斐的神谕就用个刨花板和灵魂世界沟通？
You think the Delphic Oracles used a chipboard to commune with the spirit world?
*Delphic Oracles*
*古希腊德尔斐阿波罗神庙的祭司，传能与阿波罗沟通，传授其神谕*
他们的板子也是台湾制造？
Were their boards also, made in Taiwan?
我又没说这就是他们用的那个
I never said it was original.
但是，同样威力无比
But,no less powerful.
好吧
Well
我赌一德拉克马
one drachma
*德拉克马 古希腊货币单位*
你的板子预个言的能力也就跟我的八号球一样挫
says that your plaque is as good predicting the future as my big old 8 balls.
*8 ball 一种常见少儿玩具，球内液体中有一些答案标签*
*问问题时手摇球，标签即会浮上显示*
你怎么能拿预言打赌!
You can't gamble on prophecy!
这简直是用潘朵拉盒子放电视遥控器的节奏！
That's like using Pandora's box as a handy place to keep your TV remote.
我就知道
Just what I thought.
你想我证明？好
You want a proof? Fine.
轰……轰……
Ommm....Ommmm....
你特么在干嘛？
What the hell are you doing?
你看不出来吗？
What's it look like?
哼哼哼哼哼
Ohmmm...
看起来像你下凡时头先着了地了
It looks like you are dropped on your head.
行了，我受够了
Ok, I've had enough.
好了好了，天
Ok, alright, Geez.
我算知道Stella为啥把你甩了
I'm starting to see why Stella curved your ass.
和预言者交流是很严肃的
Channeling the Oracle is serious
还有，跟你说
and just for the record
爷才是那提分手的人
I'm the one who did the curving.
好了好了，我会乖的
OK. I'll behave.
闭上眼，清空你的大脑
Close your eyes,clear your mind.
反正也没什么可清的
It shouldn't be too hard.
你准备好了就问问题吧
And when you are ready,ask your question.
哪位美女正想我呢？
Which fine woman is thinking about me right now?
-板子答案：Kenzi-
看到了吧
You see?
你让板子这么回答的
You ordered the board to do that.
我怎么可能会知道？
How would I know that?
其实每个人都看出来奸情了
Everybody knows that.
好吧，这次问个严肃点的
Alright,serious question this time.
为了你的钱
To your money.
我之后的下任Ash是谁？
Who will replace me as the next Ash?
Hale?
汝当备迎斯人
Prepare yourselves for the arrivals.
言之必应
The prophecy shall be fulfilled.
枕戈待旦
Prepare.
摩厉以须
未雨绸缪
Prepare.
啊
Ah
我觉得这东西就是个假货
I think this thing is a fake.
跟你做生意真爽
Pleasure doing business with you.
Una Mens
The Una Mens.
做好准备
Prepare.
看完了
Here we go
多了点背景故事然后……
A little bit more bad story and...
巫术板总是让我害怕
Ouija boards always freak me out.
没错（我也是）
Yeah (me too)
我们请James Earl Jones配的音还是那就是你？
Did we hire James Earl Jones to do that voice or it was just you?
*James Earl Jones  星战中Darth Vader的扮演者 *
没有啦亲我不过是……
No baby I just went from the...
恩那就是你（都是我）
Yeah that was all you(That's all I did)
我们就知道
We knew it
哦那真是棒
Oh so that was great
进段广告
So we are gonna go to a commercial break now
我们稍候回来
but when we get back
回答一些问题，再看个网络剧
we'll answer more questions and see another webisode
不要走开
So, stay tuned
嗨，我是Kris Holden-Ried，欢迎回来
Hi I'm Kris Holden-Ried. Welcome back to the Clubhouse
我们在讲最爱的妖女故事，网络剧
Where we were talking about our favorite Lost Girl stories, webisodes,
还有准备第四季今天晚上的首播
and getting ready for the big season 4 premier tonight
即刻推出
It's coming out very soon
所以请别走开
So don't go anywhere
因为我们要从魔术盒里抽点问题
Cause we're gonna have a little bit more questions from the magic box
终于该我玩魔术盒了
Yes it's my turn of the magic box
来自Tracy Adkingson，Bo靠吸食性能量而活
So, from Tracy Adkingson, Bo needs to feed off of others' sexual energy to survive
是的
Yes
如果你要靠吸食一样东西而活，会是什么
If you had to feed off of any one thing to survive, what would it be
随便什么特大号披撒
Any deluxe Pizza
我要选欢笑，怎么样？
I vote, laughter. How's that one
因为我喜欢逗人笑，因此他们一笑
Cause I like making people laugh, so when they laugh
我就可以吸食他们的笑
then I can feed off of that laughter
对我来说没什么比善良来得更感动了
For me, nothing moves me more in life when people are genuinely kind
我要吸食善良
So I would feed off of kindness
那我也得深刻了，我本来想的是吃的
See now I gotta get all deep, I was just thinking like planting, or burrito
但是我现在必须要深刻一把
But now I gotta get deep
下个问题来自Leslie Damiko
So, next question's from Leslie Damiko
能给我们讲讲难忘的和粉丝见面的经历吗？
Can any of the actors tell us about memorable moments meeting fans
我觉得讲到粉丝，我们真是幸运
I think we've all been very lucky in terms getting like really cool
有那么多粉丝艺术作品，海报，画
Fanart, posters, paintings...
但是我觉得我有个能称雄所有的东西
But, I think I got one to top this, and I'm really excited about this
我要隆重介绍小Kenzi
I want to introduce the world, the little Kenzi
一个很有天分的艺术家Ms. Joe Moggsie做了这个
who was made by a very talented artist by the name of Ms. Joe Moggsie
小Kenzi什么都有，黑皮内衣，雷帝嘎嘎鞋
And little Kenzi's got everything for like a black leather bra, to like Lady Gaga heels,
发型，小手铐
you know the right-hair-do, and a little cuffs
她要被慈善拍卖
And she's actually gonna be auctioned off for charity
所以你们当中的某人会带她回家
So hopefully one of you guys at home, will have little Kenzi one day soon
我不知道我的能否强过这个
I don't know if I got one to top that
但我有个很有趣的故事
But I've got an interesting one
这个剧有好多前军队的粉丝
Well like obviously this show has a lot of ex-military fans
我在亚特兰大的时候
So when we were down at Atlanta
和一粉丝促膝长谈
I had this really..very very deep conversation with this one fan
她给了我个硬币
so she gave me this coin
她说，要是我遇到任何军队的人
so she said, if you meet anybody in the military
给他们看这个硬币
and you show them this coin
他们要是没带
if they don't have their coin
就得依法，军队法律，给我买酒
they by law, military law, have to buy you a drink
啥？！
what?!
上周我在纽约
so I was in New York just last week
这个可爱的年轻妹子
This young girl, she was really lovely
她正在服役
and she's actually in the military
刚从阿富汗回来
she has just come back from Afghanistan, so..
我还真带了
I actually had it in my pocket
我知道我带了
I know I have that
我就拿出放桌上
So I pulled it out of my jacket and put it on the table
她停下了，跑去了街对面
She stopped, ran out, went cross the street,
拿个棕色纸袋（啥？）回来，里面装了啤酒
came back with a brown paper bag (what?!) with a beer inside it
放在了我桌上
And put it on my desk
太棒了（啥也没问）
That's awesome(No questions asked)
真好（真棒，真好）
That's nice(That's cool, that's pretty good)
但是没那个那么好
But it's not as cool as that
来自DVpandemic
from DVpandemic
你们对Tamsin和Bo的关系/感情怎么看？
What is your view on the chemistry/relationship between Tamsin and Bo
噢噢噢……（没有的事）
Wooo...(it doesn't exist)
恩……我说……我真是爱死你了
emmm...I mean...I just love you
和你产生火花好容易
It is so easy to have chemistry with you
我觉得，你就是人群中那个，要知道
I feel that...you are one of those people,you know,where...
不是单我这么觉得
I didn't exclusively feel this
每个人都这么觉得
I think everybody feel this way
遇到你，就像……
when meet you,and it's like
你会觉得，倾盖如故
you feel like you've known you forever
噢……谢啦, Rachel
Awww,thank you,Rachel.
*本段播出同时，Anna在Twitter上@Rachel回复表白：Love you too*
还有……你吸引力爆棚，挺好……
And... You're hot, so that's cool.
我觉得对我和Rachel来说最好玩的就是
But I think what was interesting for Rachel and I is that,you know,
Tamsin和Bo一开始合不来
Tamsin and Bo didn't exactly hit it off in the beginning
但是Rachel和Anna（却很合得来）
But, Rachel and Anna did
所以我们就得提醒自己
So we had to kind of remind ourselves like
我们恨对方我们恨对方我们恨对方
"We hate each other!We hate each other!We hate each other!"
开演。对，我们恨对方
Action,Yeah hate each other,exactly
但我觉得Bo和Tamsin尊重对方
but I think there's a mutual respect between Bo and Tamsin.
她们势均力敌，你懂
They are equals, you know.
她们都很强大
They're very powerful.
我觉得火花里尊重是个要素
So I think there's a respect in the chemistry kind of...exist there
即使她俩不总是赞同对方的选择
Even they may not always love each other's choices,
她们尊重这些选择
they kind of respect them.
你们知道我想知道什么吗
You know what I want to know guys?
我想知道演邪恶的Vex是什么感觉
I want to know what's it like to play the evil monstrous Vex
恩，是啥感觉呢
Ah what it is like
对，强大的Mesmer是什么感觉
Yeah what is it like to be the all powerful Mesmer
演Vex真是太影响我了
It's like the most powerful thing ever playing Vex
穿上他那些皮裤
Just to be able to get in those leather pants
每天我来拍摄现场
everyday I come into set
做那些甩手动作
and and just do the hand movements
没事的，别担心
it's Ok, don't worry
我们能看看我吗？
can we just watch me now?
闭上你的眼睛想像一下
Close your peepers for one hot second,and imagine this.
焦糖酱喷泉
Dulce de Leche fountains
大到查理辛都为之折服
big enough for Charlie Sheen's ego.
*Charlie Sheen 演员，因为人自大被踢出了剧集<好汉两个半>*
来宾们秀色可餐
Guests so delicious
连模特都食欲焕发
they'll make a model wanna eat.
*意指模特经常断食*
还有服装!
And the outfits!
艾玛那些服装！
Fooah the outfits.
他们会让Jean Paul Gaultier的春季新品
They will make Jean Paul Gaultier's spring collech (collection)
*Jean Paul Gaultie 法国著名设计师*
看起来和敬老院自制的贝壳面项链一样挫
look like a 'string your own macaroni necklace day' at the geriatric ward.
我们在讨论的是
We are talking about
为了长了一点尾巴的我，而开的世纪派对
the party of the century for little old me.
灯光
Spot light
音乐
Symphony
Vex，Hale在一号线上
Vex,Hale on line one.
他说这他今天第七次打电话给你了
He says it's the 7th time he’s tried to call you today.
我忙着呢！
I’m Busy!
出场
Entrance!
所有人都看着我
All eyes on me
当我从血钻吊灯上降落
as I descend on the blood diamond chandelier.
百度百科，你必须等它们降下来以后才能清洗它们
Fact,they descend because that’s how you clean them apparently.
喘息，欢呼，泪花，荷尔蒙
Gasps,applause,tears,boners!
欢迎光临新暗黑时代!
Welcome to the start of the new dark era!
现在，庆祝过后，我的客人们想要一些小吃
Now,after the festivities,my guests would want some nosh.
那就是你出场的时刻
And that's where you come in.
因为你是这个地球上唯一愿意料理河豚的人
Now you are the only chef on the continent that is willing to prepare fugu.
富含氰化物的鱼
The cyanide fish
*事实上河豚毒素的毒性大约是氰化物的1200倍*
不好好做就是吃必死
prepared incorrectly it will kill instantly.
为什么你的推荐人都被划掉了？
Now, why have all your references been crossed off?
Alyssa
我能为你做什么吗?
What can I do for you?
恩，尝尝河豚
Ah, Try the fugu.
我，我是全素者
I..I..I'm vegan.
*指所有动物制品（包括蛋、奶）都不吃的严格素食主义者*
哎哟喂～我系全素主义者
Yewww...I'm vegan.
看在亲耐的曾被称为王子的艺术家的份上
For the lovely artist formerly known as Prince
*Prince 王子 歌手，一度使用别的艺名，因此有”曾被称为王子”一说*
告诉我你已经定好会场了
tell me you booked the venue.
恩，实际上他们刚答复我了
Yeah actually,they just got back to me...
想都表想给我坏消息
Don't you dare think about giving me bad news.
呃，因为那个庄园是政府所有
Ahh,since the chateau is part government property
他们要你提交申请
they require an application
而且流程要等上好几个月
and the process takes months.
那么我们的后备计划呢?
What about plan B?
宴会轮船
The party boat
恩我知道，是显得有点普通
yeah I mean, I know its a tad common
可我们没得可选啊
but see how many choice we got left?
哈佛晚上九点以后，不让放吵闹的音乐
The harvard laws have restrictions on loud music after 9pm
客人的人数也有限制
and restrictions on number of guest.
我们不能接待一千五百个人
We can't accommodate 1500 people.
我们需要许可证，这要花上……
It would require a permit,and it would take...
让我猜猜，花上好几个月
Let me guess,months?
是滴
Hmmm.
开个派对有多难
How hard is it to arrange a party?!
对，这就是你想要的么，Vex ？
Yeah, is that what you want, Vex?
恩，今天不行，小甜甜
Yeah, not today sugar puffs.
你说窒息就跟亲热似的
You said choking is that you’re making out.
是，但是你让我很不高兴
Yeah, but you've made me very upset.
这个宴会超级重要
This party is everything.
我觉得我把什么都干了
I feel like I'm doing all the work.
就跟唱独角戏似的！
A bloody one man show!
可我唯一喜欢的独角戏
And the only one man show that I fancy is a...
是穿皮裤洗澡时自弹自唱，懂？
a long shower in chaps, Ya?
要我去为你准备沐浴吗？
Shall I start the shower for you?
我表
Negative.
我会给你找个新的会场，会更好更强大
I'll find you another venue,it'll be even better.
有游泳池，还有……
With a pool,and...emm…
螺旋梯供你闪亮登场
a winding staircase for your grand entrances.
不如来个闪亮退场如何？
How about a grand exit?
吃!河!豚!
Try.the.fugu.
河豚死你
Fugu you.
你被雇佣了，只要我们能找到会场
You are hired, providing we can find a venue.
嘿，你，下一个
Hey you! Next!
你好
Hello.
我有什么能为你效劳的
What can I do for you?
你说话得大点声，亲
You’ll have to use your outside voice, darling.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
叶子媚
May.
啊，李丽珍，太好了，现在
Ahh, perfect, Alyssa,now.
伦家就只是想搞个宴会
I simply am trying to throw a party
但是总是碰一鼻子灰
but I keep running into red tape.
我希望你能让那些条条款款都消失
Now I'd like you to make that red tape vanish
就算它还在那，我也不想听
and if it's still there, I don't want to hear anything about it
因为你的任务就是想办法绕过它
because it's your job to find a way around it.
明白了吗
Got it?
啊，真是苦差事啊亲
Ahh...It's hard work, darling.
我是说，条条框框，无能下属
I mean, restrictions, incompetent people.
我不过想办个宴会罢了
I'm just simply trying to throw a party.
我要是认真起来会怎么样啊？
What's gonna happen when I try to do something serious?
我都干了啥？
What have I done?
包裹？
Package?
哦，是的，这很不可思议，我知道
Oh, yeah, it's impressive, I know.
在澳大利亚，介叫便当
In Australia, they call it a packed lunch.
你就放桌上吧
You can just put it on the desk.
好
OK.
*目测如尼文，会翻译的大神请联系字幕组(￣￣* )g*
投影仪？
Projector?
赶紧的
Quickly.
还有把厨子解决掉
And kill the caterer.
宴会结束了
The party is over.
你穿皮革还真不错呢Paul
Woo you do look good in leather Paul
好笑的事，你知道吗
yeah the funny thing about that is you know..
我每次都一次性的做那个
I actually do that all in one every single time
很难做好
which is pretty tricky
那是挺难的
that's a mouthful
是的是的没错
yeah yeah exactly
主要因为我是受过正规训练的演员
Largely 'cause I am the only classical trained actor amongst these all
没错
this is correct
稍后我们会回来讲述更多演员的事
Anyway we'll be back soon with more from the Lost Girl cast
不要走开
Stay tuned
嘿，我是Rachel Skarsten，欢迎回来
Hi, I'm Rachel Skarsten, and we are back in the clubhouse
首播还几分钟了，来看粉丝问题吧
We are minutes away from the premier so let's get right back to our fans
这个问题来自Alexandra Dessau
This one is from Alexandra Dessau
填空，这季是――――空格
finish this sentence: this season is more ____blank
无敌
Epic
啊你个小偷！
Ah you stealer!
我正想说那个！
That's what I was gonna say
魔幻，戏剧？
Magical, theatrical?
和你所知道的相去甚远
It's more of the opposite of what you think you know
对，对
Yes, Yeah
比右边左一点
It's a lot more left than right
对
Yes
比以前更圆
It's more circular than it's ever been
多少不那么中心
it's more less center
更高
It's taller
是香蕉
It's bananas
更宽
It's a little wider
更像独角兽
It's more unicorn
有时候它会躺下
Sometimes it lies down
偶尔沉没一下
Occasionally it's sinked
好的，下个问题，好，谢谢
Ok, next question, great thank you.
Zoie Palmer!
这个问题是Billy Macathy问大家的
This one is from Billy Macathy, for everyone
在个人生活和演艺生涯中切换是什么样的
What's it like bouncing your personal lives and your professional lives
噢，我们住这（的确）
Woo...we live here(yeah we do)
这就像我们的第二个家
This is kind of like our seconds family
不过我觉得我们的真的家人挺想我们的
But I think our real families do miss us
作为演员来说很有趣
it's interesting because when we work as actors
因为在角色和自己之间有很多转换
there's a lot of transfer sometimes between the character that we play and the person we are
但我发现Skyler
But I found with Skyler
每次我看着Skyler，就如同……
everytime, when I see the Skyler, there's a wash
经历了一场洗礼
A clean wash
我就想我要做个最好的人，最好的爸爸
Like I just wish I can be the best person, the best dad I could be for the kid..
就像Ksenia和我对Max和Tino一样
That's like how Ksenia and I feel about Max and Tino
就想对他们最好
We want to be the best people we can be for them(yeah)
然后（给他们买最好的狗粮）
And...(feed them the best Kibble)
当然了，最好的狗粮
The best Kibble of course
说得真好，Rachel
That's beautiful, Rachel
老实说妖女剧组真是个很棒的大家庭
Emm honestly we have a pretty amazing family in Lost Girl which you can see
有时候嘛事情好笑过了头
Sometimes things get pretty hilarious
我们来看看一些我们耍乌龙的瞬间吧
Let's take a look at some moments that didn't go too well for a couple of us
恩恩
Ugh uh..
哦天啊
Oh my God
我跟你这个黑暗精灵握个手，就欠你了？
So I shook hands with the dark pixie and now I owe you my i-owe-you?
恩没错，就是
yeah, ugh huh yes
你得剪头发了
You deserve a hair cut
好抱歉！我打到Kris的蛋蛋了
I'm so sorry! I just hit Kris in the balls
说真的，你到底是啥啊
Seriously, what are you
不是你杀得死的，Bo-bo
Something you can't kill, Bo-Bo
但那个可能会杀了你
But this might kill you
真不好意思啊
I'm so sorry guys...
谁特么乱动我东西了
Someone's being fucking with my mojo?
真感谢能够成为你们的一员
Guys thank you very much for having me
我得赶飞机去了
I have to go to make a flight
但其他人稍后会回来
But everyone else will be back very soon
亲亲
Muah!
爱你（爱你）再见！
Love you (love you), bye!
嗨，好，我是Zoie Palmer
Hi.Hello I'm Zoie Palmer.
欢迎回来
Welcome back to the clubhouse.
我真是不停的吃爆米花
I literally can't stop eating pop corn.
都吃第七盒了
I'm on my 7th box of popcorn here.
第四季首播就快开始了
The s4 premier is coming out very soon,
我们都很兴奋
we're all very excited.
但我们还是有点时间回答粉丝提问
But we still have some time for some more fan questions.
这个问题来自Angela Romano
This one is from Angela Romano?.
我们会知道一些Kenzi和Lauren的过去吗
"Will we learn more about Kenzi and Lauren's back story?"
只要和我有关，看看
(Anything about me.)(Look at that.)
我觉得，没错，有Lauren的过去
I think, yes,we do learn more about Lauren's back story.
我们会知道些……她究竟有什么问题
We'll learn a bit more about what...what her problem is.
还有……我不知道……
And...I don't know.
你呢肯子
What about you Kenz?
我觉得……是……我们会深入Kenzi的过去
I think we...yeah,we dive into Kenzi's past,
有些……怪胎出现了
and some...some peeps appear.
不能说太多哈
without giving too much away
但是给了Kenzi一些希望
emmm,who kind of shed some light on Kenzi's life
还有她是从哪来的
and where she comes from
好了，我们要做个视频问题
Ok.We're gonna go on to a video question.
请看大屏幕
We're gonna to watch the monitor.
嗨，我是Anna
Hi.I'm Anna.
我的问题是Kenzi和Lauren这季能当朋友吗
My question is will Kenzi and Lauren be friends this season?
我希望如此
I hope so.
她问Kenzi和Lauren能不能当朋友
She said will Kenzi and Lauren be friends this season.
我希望如此
I hope so.
哦天啊
Oh my god...
第三季结束，我们终于……你知道
Well,the end of s3,we finally,you know,
该说的都说了
dish it out?,talk things out.
对我们有这场戏
Yeah,we had that scene where we were big grumpy.
然后我们就……我记得那场暴力戏（非常暴力）
And then we got...I remember that grumpy scene.(Very grumpy.)
我们联手砍猪
We fought pigs together.
真好
That was nice.
我觉得吧……
So I feel like...you know...
我们正朝那努力
We're getting there.
我们有过互相刻薄的时候
We've had grumpy,mean,you know,times,
我觉得是时候该Kenzi和Lauren相亲相爱了
I feel like it's time to get into the...love with Kenzi in Lauren.
嘿，又到网络剧时间
Hey I know it's webisode time.
我们今年要介绍全新的异种
and we are introducing a whole other kind of Fae this year.
我们给过提示
We've hinted about that.
在一个我们参加过的活动里
It's on one of the conventions we've attended
是时候认识些异种界的新人了
But now it's time to get to know a little more about some of the new players in the Fae world this year,
或者说，旧人
or rather some of the old players.
Faedonia电影公司为您呈现
The Faedonia Film Company presents
认识你
Getting to know you.
第二章，Una Mens
Chapter 2. The Una Mens.
*目测同Ep02一样的如尼文及楔形文合体，会翻译的大神请联系字幕组*
哦，又见面了
Oh,well hello again.
是我，您的老朋友Flynn Decker
It's me,your old pal Flynn Decker.
我衷心希望您喜欢上周“认识你”的讲座
I so hope you enjoyed last week's presentation of Getting to Know You.
第一章 血圣的失踪
Chapter 1,the disappearance of the Blood King
当然了，它将我们带到了
which of course, brings us to the creation of
Una Mens的创始
the Una Mens.
他们是谁？
Who are they?
他们都干些什么？
What do they do?
他们对于你我有何意义？
What do they mean to you or I?
我自然会如实奉告
Well I'll tell you sure enough
但我们为何不先谈谈我们所知道的
but why don't we first find out what you know already
然后再从那里开始
and go from there
他们还没来吧亲？
They are not here,are they darling?
嘿！你！
Hey,you there!
Una Mens是谁啊？
Who are the Una Mens?
我听说他们是超级英雄
I hear they are superheroes
战斗力爆表
and can throw a punch just like that
砰，磅，啪，乒
WAM, SMACK, PAW, BAM
你倒是很清楚呢，Buzz
You're sure, Buzz
可Mogsy却不这么想
but not our Mogsy
我听说他们是一群吓人的妖怪
I hear there was the boogeymans.
*Boogeyman 大人用来吓小朋友的怪物，类似狼外婆*
哦，对不起，小不点
Oh no sorry little one.
他们是Una Mens，恩
That's Una Mens.Hmmm...
看来我们需要一点帮助
Well it looks like we are gonna need a little help.
Una Mens是异种长老们的得力干将
The Una Mens are the near omniscient in the fashion of Fae Elders
主要职责是铁血执法
whose sole purpose is to enforce the laws
以死亡之痛确保血圣写的法律得以实施
written on the King of Blood with pain of death.
您明白了吗？
Is it enough for you?
Una Mens抓走了我的儿子！
Una Mens took my son!
我的孩子！
My boy!
我希望他们都去死！
And I want them dead!
要我说，他们应该都应该被拉去绞刑台吊死
If you ask me,they should be strung up,brought to the gallows
最好碎尸万段！
and whipped out of guts!
不！别！
No! No!
啊哦，看来有些人忘了Una Mens的三R法则
Eh Oh,it looks like somebody has forgotten the three "R"s of the Una Mens.
克制，尊重，否则秋后算账
Restrain.Respect.or Reckoning.
挺简单的其实
It's all quite simply really.
守法的异种公民们没什么好怕的
There's nothing to fear for the law-abiding citizens of the Fae world.
我们务必要保持冷静，继续生活
We must keep calm and carry on.
然后记住
And remember
如果我们尽量克制，遵守异种的法律
If we show restraint,and respect the laws of the Fae
就不会有……
there will be no...
不会有……
no...
Buzz，该你了！
Buzz,that's your cue!
不会有秋后算账
No reckoning.
干的好，小伙子！
Nice one, junior.
有你这光明派的姿态
Well with a nice Light Fae attitude like that
将来准保能参选Ash
you're sure in for Ash one day.
哦……恩……或者代理Ash？
Oh...well...maybe acting Ash?
谁都别他妈拦我……
Why I oughtta?
*出自著名喜剧The Three Stooges*
是吗小伙子？
Is it junior?
记住了，血律里杠杠的事实
Remember,straight one truth from the Blood laws
大概Johnson夫人今年感恩节的火鸡会小一点了
Let's just say that Mrs.Johnson's turkey's gonna be a little bit smaller this thanksgiving.
下地狱去吧！
Go to hell!
冷静点Johnson夫人
Oh calm down Mrs.Johnson.
我们必须遵守Una Men的三R原则
We must observe the three "R"s of the Una Mens
因为要是没了他们，就会一片混乱
for without them,there will be chaos.
没人想要那样
And nobody wants that.
因此，看吧，朋友们
So you see friends
生活是多么的美好
life is honesty goodness fate
简单得就像一个……
is as easy as one...
简单得就像……
is as easy as....
克制？
Restraint?
我说不下去了
I can't do this anymore.
这特么到底是什么东西啊？
This? What the hell is this. Huh?
这是死亡异种之书吗？
Is this a book of dead Fae?
这里面都是死掉的异种的照片吗？
Is this with the pictures of dead Fae in there?
怎么？他们按你们要求做了
What? Did they do what you said
然后你还对他们这样？
So...so you do this?
我认识他们其中的一些人！
I know some of these people!
怎么我是下一个吗？
What am I next?
告诉你，兄弟！
I got news for you,pal!
你不能抓我！
You can't have me!
因为我是Flynn Decker
Cuz I only answer Flynn Decker
是Flynn Decker！
and Flynn Decker only!
别碰我！
No take your hands off me!
不！别！
No! No!
不要！不要啊！
哦那真棒，是吧
Ok that was awesome, aye?
吓人
Creepy.
真有点吓人
and a little terrified.
离首播越来越近了
We're getting closer to the premier of Lost Girl.
千万别走开
So do not go anywhere.
好了，欢迎回来
Alright guys,welcome back to the clubhouse.
我们好激动，控制不了了
We're so excited.We can't even contain ourselves,
因为你们马上就要看到首播了
because you guys are about to see the s4 premier,Ok.
在那之前，我们再回答点粉丝问题吧
So before we do that,we're gonna get a couple more fan questions then before we go,alright?
哟，别吃爆米花了
Yo! No pop corns.
盒子给我
Hand over the box.
好了，这个问题来自Bree Amber Yeumanz
Alright.This is from Bree Amber Yeumanz
是问Zoie的
This is for Zoie.
亲，这个问题是
And the question is,my love
记Lauren的那些医学名词什么的难吗
"Was it hard learning all those medical terms and phrases Lauren says?
其他人呢？你们怎么准备的
How about everyone else? How do you prepare for scenes?"
很难，挺难
Yes,it's hard.It is hard.
有时候我完全不知道我在说什么
I sometimes have no idea what I'm saying.
我真是死记硬背，然后说
I literally just memorized it phonetically,and then say it.
那么其他小伙伴们呢？你们怎么准备的？
How about everyone else?How do you guys prepare?
我妥妥的问了谷娘和维基娘关于异种的问题
I definitely google and wikipedia different fae stuff
因为，我需要在脑里有个构图神马
Cuz it's...yeah,I need to have a picture of something in my head
我是想给你们讲个故事
when I'm trying to tell you guys the stories.
我走在片场，我闻着角落，我四处撒尿
I walk on set, I smell in corners,I pee on things
对着陌生人狼嚎
And you know I'm like just basically growl at stranger
妥妥的，要修炼多年瑜伽才能做到
And yes,well that took years of yoga,Paul.
不要贬低哥的练习
Don't diminish my training.
我们进场的第一件事情
Getting in here and then going into the hair make up trailer
就是去做发型
which is usually the first thing that we do.
我开始感觉到越来越像Bo
I slowly start to feel more and more like Bo.
然后我就穿上紧身裤
And as soon as I put on the tight pants
然后事业线呼吁而出
and the... the cleavage comes out,
皮带一穿
and the belt goes on
然后Anna就消失了
And the Anna goes away.
对，然后Anna就消失了
Yeah,the Anna goes away.
我是谁？
Who am I?
我真的需要
I really need...
我真的需要大干一场
I really feel ready to kick some ass.
我想知道妖女还有一小会儿就开演了
I wonder how you guys at home feeling knowing
在家等待的小伙伴们怎么看？
that we are mere moments away from the epic s4 premiere.
就快开演了，我们还有最后一个问题
We are this close,but we got one more question.
所以这是特别的最后一问
So this is the special last question.
兴奋
(Excited.)
我伸手进异种箱
I'm gonna reaching into the Fae box.
我要把问题拿出来
I'm gonna pull it out.
这个问题，来自Janet Shawn
The question is,from Janet Shawn
我们知道你不能透露第四季的剧情，但是给我们点甜头吧
"We know you can't give away s4,but throw us a bone."
哦，额滴神啊
Oh...Gosh...Wow.
谈论第四季太难了
It is so hard to talk about s4.
因为第三季结尾抖的包袱
Because we have so many cliffhangers in the end of s3.
我不能说我觉得你不会失望
I can't say I do feel like you won't be disappointed.
你不会失望
You will not be disappointed.
这季很好很强大
It is a strong season.
很多的反转和扭曲，还有神秘啦，秘密啦，火辣啦
There are so many twists and turns,and mysteries,and secrets,and sexiness.
而且你会看到你从未看过的
And I think each of the character you're gonna see them
每一个角色的不同面
in the way you've never quite seen them before.
我觉得每个人都是这样
I think that's the case of all of us.
我不认为有任何一个角色
I don't think there's any one of us
你会没点惊奇的小发现
that you're not gonna get it to know a little bit more about little bit of a surprise
我们都等不及听到你们的反馈了
We can't wait to hear what you guys think.
我会知道我们会再聊的
I'm sure we'll talk to you guys very soon.
我们希望你们喜欢妖女第四季
We hope you love it.
这季变大，变坏
This season got big, and got bad
我们现在就为你奉上
We're gonna to bring it to you right now.
没错
Yes,we are.
谢谢所有粉丝精彩的问题
And thank you very much to all of our fans for great questions.
今晚我们知道了很多信息
We all learned a lot tonight.
我们很享受拍第四季
And we had a great time filming s4.
我们也很希望你们也享受第四季
And we really hope that you all enjoy it.
还有几秒钟就开播了
It's coming up just a few seconds.
所以哪都别去
So,don't go anywhere.
白啦小伙伴们
Bye everyone!
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  r(st)q
英文字幕：Naya，ABCChipmunk，Joy
听译：Momo，李夹碎，Neffititi，骷髅头正宫_K    时间轴：ABCChipmunk，Neffititi，李夹碎，潜行的五
校对：Neffititi，潜行的五    特效、精校：潜行的五    压制：潜行的五
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途